const questions = [
  {
    question: "If a triangle has equal angles then the triangle is ?",
    options: ["scalene", "equilateral", "isosceles", "all"],
    answer: "equilateral",
    id: "zero"
  },
  {
    question: "If a triangle has two equal angles then the triangle can be ?",
    options: ["equilateral", "isosceles", "both", "none of these"],
    answer: "both",
    id: "one"
  },
  {
    question: "If a triangle has base 14cm and height 5cm then the area is ?",
    options: ["35sqcm", "30sqcm", "30sqcm", "not enough information"],
    answer: "35sqcm",
    id: "two"
  },
  {
    question: "A triangle with one angle greater than 90 degrees is called ?",
    options: ["scalene", "equilateral", "obtuse", "acute"],
    answer: "obtuse",
    id: "three"
  },
  {
    question: "A triangle with all three angles less than 90 degrees ?",
    options: ["scalene", "equilateral", "obtuse", "acute"],
    answer: "acute",
    id: "four"
  },
  {
    question: "A triangle having at least two equal sides ?",
    options: ["scalene", "equilateral", "isosceles", "all"],
    answer: "isosceles",
    id: "five"
  },
  {
    question: "A triangle with one angle equal to 90 degrees. ?",
    options: ["scalene", "acute", "isosceles", "right"],
    answer: "right",
    id: "six"
  },
  {
    question: "The sum of the measures of all three sides of a triangle ?",
    options: ["area", "perimeter", "volume", "none of these"],
    answer: "perimeter",
    id: "seven"
  },
  {
    question: "In right triangle, the side opposite to right angle is called ?",
    options: ["altitude", "hypotenuse", "angle bisector", "none of these"],
    answer: "hypotenuse",
    id: "eight"
  },
  {
    question:
      "The perimeter of a equilateral triangle is 15cm. What is the length of one side ?",
    options: ["3", "45", "15", "5"],
    answer: "5",
    id: "nine"
  }
];

export default questions;
